Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ nursenicolexoxo (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

TNCC

Certified pediatric emergency nurse Pediatric Nursing

Certifications

Certified Pediatric Emergency Nurse
Pediatric Advanced Life Support
BLS

Honors-Awards

Daisy Award For Extraordinary Nurses

Nicole Rogers

Registered Nurse and Founder of Mommy Magic Wellness Houston, Texas Area

Summary

I am dedicated to delivering high quality evidence based holistic care that transform healthcare and addresses public healthcare initiatives and crisis

Founder of Mommy Magic Wellness geared toward empowering and supporting women and their children to address and correct public health issues.

I have worked in nationally ranked hospitals as an Award Winning Certified Pediatric Emergency Room Nurse, Breastfeeding Resource Nurse, a leader in hospital initiatives and preceptorship.

Experience in public speaking.

Wealth of knowledge of policies and procedures and training competent nurses.

Experience

Texas Children's Hospital 4 years 4 months

Pediatric Registered Nurse/ Preceptor February 2015 - May 2019 (4 years 4 months)

Pediatric Registered Nurse February 2015 - May 2019 (4 years 4 months)

Fusion Medical Staffing
Travel Nurse
March 2017 - October 2017 (8 months)
Gastroenterology Procedures

Education

Prairie View A&M University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2010 - 2014)